{
    "subject": "resource/Code_Two",
    "predicate": "ontology/abstract",
    "object": "Code Two is a 1953 film about men training to be motorcycle cops. It stars Ralph Meeker, Sally Forrest, Elaine Stewart and Robert Horton and was directed by Fred M. Wilcox.",
    "human_readable": "The abstract of Code Two is that it's a 1953 film about men training to be motorcycle cops, starring Ralph Meeker, Sally Forrest, Elaine Stewart, and Robert Horton, and directed by Fred M. Wilcox.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.8447836637496948,
            "question": "What type of training are the men in Code Two undergoing?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8370185494422913,
            "question": "What is the profession that the men in Code Two are training for?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.8049308657646179,
            "question": "Who directed the film Code Two?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7538797855377197,
            "question": "Can you describe the setting of the film Code Two?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7050172090530396,
            "question": "What year was the film Code Two released?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6297978162765503,
            "question": "What is the main plot of Code Two?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.6169248223304749,
            "question": "Name one actor who starred in Code Two."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5954077243804932,
            "question": "Name three actors who appeared in Code Two."
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5654990077018738,
            "question": "Who plays the lead role in Code Two?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5387198328971863,
            "question": "What genre is Code Two likely to be classified as?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=The abstract of Code Two is that it's a 1953 film about men training to be motorcycle cops, starring Ralph Meeker, Sally Forrest, Elaine Stewart, and Robert Horton, and directed by Fred M. Wilcox.",
            "html": "dbpedia_368_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who plays the lead role in Code Two?",
            "html": "dbpedia_368_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name three actors who appeared in Code Two.",
            "html": "dbpedia_368_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Name one actor who starred in Code Two.",
            "html": "dbpedia_368_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_126.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_131.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_151.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_153.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_16.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_42.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_47.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_49.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "dbpedia_368_78.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n```  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 0,
            "full_ans": "{\n  \"output\": \"no\"\n}"
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe provided abstract accurately summarizes the content of the documents regarding \"Code Two,\" including its year (1953), genre (a film about men training to be motorcycle cops), main actors (Ralph Meeker, Sally Forrest, Elaine Stewart, and Robert Horton), and director (Fred M. Wilcox)."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {'output': 'yes'}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "qwen2.5:14b": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "More Popular",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {
        "llama3.1": {
            "reason": "The claim is wrong because the film Code Two is actually a 1955 film, not a 1953 one.",
            "category": 3
        }
    }
}